Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
- Bureau of Labor Statistics, Technological Change - Burstin, Carolyn., Publication (Box 4)
  - Changing Employment and Skills Formation in Service Industries: A Comparison of Supermarkets, Department Stores, Software Firms and Hospitals in France, Japan, Sweden and the US., 1989; Publication (Box 4, Folder 66)
    May 1989
    - Item 1: Changing Employment and Skill Formation in Service Industries: A Comparison of Supermarkets, Department Stores, Software Firms and Hospitals in France, Japan, Sweden and the United States, 1989; Publication (Box 4, Folder 66)
      Author: Olivier Bertrand and Thierry Noyelle
  - Human Resources and Corporate Strategy: Technological Change in Banks and Insurance Companies in France, Germany, Japan, Sweden and the US., 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 67)
    November 1987
    - Item 1: Human Resources and Corporate Strategy: Technological Change in Banks and Insurance Companies in France, Germany, Japan, Sweden and the United States, 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - "Societal Implications of Advanced Manufacturing Technology"., 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Item 1: Societal Implications of Advanced Manufacturing of Technology, 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 68)
      Author: John Bessant and Peter Senker
  - "Productivity-Based Compensation to Foster Full-Employment and Economic Growth"., 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 69)
    April 28 1983
    - Item 1: Productivity-Based Compensation to Foster Full-Employment and Economic Growth, 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 69)
      Author: Fred Best
  - "Short-Time Compensation in North America: Trends and Prospects"., 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 70)
    January 1985
    - Item 1: Short-Time Compensation in North America: Trends and Prospects, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - "The Impact of Technological Change on Collective Bargaining Power"., 1986; Publication (Box 4, Folder 71)
    December 28 - 30 1986.
    - Item 1: The Impact of Technological Change on Collective Bargaining Power, 1986; Publication (Box 4, Folder 71)
      Author: Gordon Betcherman
  - Managing an Employee-Owned Company., 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 72)
    March 1987
    - Item 1: Managing an Employee Owned Company, 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 72)
      Author: J.R. Beyster
  - "Technology and Employment: Some Conclusions"., 1986; Publication (Box 4, Folder 73)
    March - April 1986
    - Item 1: Technology and employment: some conclusions, 1976; Publication (Box 4, Folder 73)
      Author: A.S. Bhalla
  - A Manual of Advanced Techniques for Quality Circles in the Public Sector., 1982; Publication (Box 4, Folder 74)
    May 1982
    - Item 1: A Manual of Advanced Techniques for Quality Circles in the Public Sector, 1982; Publication (Box 4, Folder 74)
      Author: Roy L. Beasley
  - Re-Energizing the Mature Organization., 1990; Publication (Box 4, Folder 75)
    Autumn 1990.
    - Item 1: Re-Energizing the Mature Organization, 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 75)
      Author: Richard W. Beattyy and David O. Ulrich
  - "Re-Energizing the Mature Organization"., Publication (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Item 1: Re-Energizing the Mature Organization, Publication (Box 4, Folder 76)
      Author: Richard W. Beatty and David O. Ulrich
  - "Implementing a Gainsharing Plan: What Companies Need to Know"., 1992; Publication (Box 4, Folder 77)
    January - February 1992
    - Item 1: Implementing a Gainsharing Plan: What Companies Need to Know, 1992; Publication (Box 4, Folder 77)
      Author: David Beck
  - "None of Us Alone Knows As Much As All of Us Together"., 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Item 1: None of Us Alone Knows as Much as All of Us Together: Participatory Learning for Worker Participation, 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 78)
      Author: John P. Beck and Janet Schneider
  - "ESOPs Aren't the Magic Key to Anything", 1989; Publication (Box 4, Folder 79)
    October 23 1989
    - Item 1: ESOPs Aren't the Magic Key to Anything, 1989; Publication (Box 4, Folder 79)
      Author: Gary S. Becker
  - "Employment Profile of the Service Sector in Selected OECD Countries"., 1989; Publication (Box 4, Folder 80)
    May 31 1989
    - Item 1: Employment Profile of the Service Sector in Selected OECD Countries, 1989; Publication (Box 4, Folder 80)
      Author: Robert W. Bednarzik
  - "Demise of 'Permanent Employment' in Japan"., 1990; Publication (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Item 1: Demise of 'Permanent Employment' in Japan, 1990; Publication (Box 4, Folder 81)
      Author: Harumi Befu and Christine Cernosia
  - "Committing to Excellence"., 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 82)
    September 25 - 26 1984
    - Item 1: J.M. Beggs, 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 82)
      Author: Committing to Excellence
  - "The National Labor Relations Act: A Potential Legal Constraint upon Quality Circles and other Employer-Sponsored Employee Committees"., 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 83)
    December 1983
    - Item 1: The National Labor Relations Act: A Potential Legal Constraint Upon Quality Circles and Other Employer-Sponsored Employee Committees, 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 83)
      Author: Curtiss K. Behrens and James R. Sollenberger
  - "Turbulent Environment, New Organizational Parameters and their Impact on Industrial Relations Systems"., 1988; Publication (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Item 1: Turbulent Environment, New Organisational Parameters and Their Impact on Industrial Relations Systems, 1988; Publication (Box 4, Folder 84)
      Author: Laurent Belanger and Michel Audet
  - "Giving Direction to Company Productivity Efforts"., 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Item 1: Giving direction to company productivity efforts, 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 85)
      Author: John Belcher
  - "An Implementation Strategy"., 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 86)
    July 1987
    - Item 1: John G. Belcher, 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 86)
      Author: An Implementation Strategy
  - "Employee Involvement Techniques"., 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Item 1: Employee Involvement Techniques, 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - The Productivity Management Process., 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Item 1: The Productivity Management Process, 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 88)
      Author: John G. Belcher
  - The Lending Environment for ESOP Companies: The Ohio Bank Study., 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Item 1: The Lending Environment for ESOP Companies: The Ohio Bank Study, 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 89)
      Author: Daniel Bell and Mark Keating
  - "Quality Circles: Making Schools Productive"., 1982; Publication (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles: Making Schools Productive, 1982; Publication (Box 4, Folder 90)
      Author: James A. Bellanca
  - "'New' Union Approach to Membership Decline: Comment"., 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 91)
    Fall 1991
    - Item 1: 'New' Union Approaches to Membership Decline: Comment, 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 91)
      Author: Don Bellante
  - Middle Class Erosion and Growing Income Inequality: Fact or Fiction?, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 92)
    November 28 1985
    - Item 1: Middle Class Erosion and Growing Income Inequality: Fact or Fiction?, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 92)
      Author: Richard S. Belous, Linda H. LeGrande, and Brian W. Cashell
  - Industrial Relations: The Minnesota Model., 1986; Publication (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Item 1: Industrial Relations: The Minnesota Model, 1986; Publication (Box 4, Folder 93)
      Author: Brian Bemmels and Mahmood A. Zaidi
  - "Manufacturing Employees and Technological Change"., 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Item 1: Manufacturing Employees and Technological Change, 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 94)
      Author: Brian Bemmels and Yonatan Reshef
  - "Professionals and Unions in Israel", 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 95)
    October 1965
    - Item 1: Professionals and Unions in Israel, Publication (Box 4, Folder 95)
      Author: Joseph Ben-David
  - "Going Beyond Continuous Improvement"., 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 96)
    September 1991
    - Item 1: Process Control for Creativity: Going Beyond Continuous Improvement, 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 96)
      Author: Steve Bender
  - "Labor Relations: Current Issues and Future Prospects"., 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Item 1: Labor Relations: Current Issues and Future Prospects, 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - "NLRB Representation and Decertification Election Statistics"., 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 98)
    April 8 1991
    - Item 1: NLRB Representation and Decertification Election Statistics, 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - 1990 Employer Bargaining Objectives., 1989; Publication (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Item 1: 1990 Employer Bargaining Objectives, 1989; Publication (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - The Comparable Worth Issue., 1981; Publication (Box 4, Folder 100)
    October 28 1981
    - Item 1: The Comparable Worth Issue, 1981; Publication (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - "Non-Traditional Incentive Pay Programs"., 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 101)
    May 1991
    - Item 1: Non-Traditional Incentive Pay Programs, 1991; Publication (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - "Recruiting and Selection Procedures"., 1988; Publication (Box 4, Folder 102)
    May 1988.
    - Item 1: Recruiting and Selection Procedures, 1988; Publication (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Unions Today: New Tactics to Tackle Tough Times., 1986; Publication (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Item 1: Unions Today: New Tactics to Tackle Tough Times, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Wage and Salary Administration., 1990; Publication (Box 4, Folder 104)
    June 1990
    - Item 1: Wage and Salary Administration, 1990; Publication (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - "Worksharing: A 'Win-Win' Concept"., 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 105)
    July 1985.
    - Item 1: Worksharing: A 'Win-Win' Concept, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 105)
      Author: James D. Burge
  - "Local Government: Why Some Agencies are Setting up 'Quality Circles'"., 1982; Publication (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Item 1: Local Government: Why Some Agencies are Setting Up 'Quality Circles', 1982; Publication (Box 4, Folder 106)
      Author: Zona Burke
  - "Employee Investment Funds: A Crucial Element in the Transition to Socialism"., 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Item 1: Employee Investment Funds: A Crucial Element in the Transition to Socialism, 1983; Publication (Box 4, Folder 107)
      Author: Brian Burkitt
  - "Control of Advanced Manufacturing Technology: Supervision Without Supervisors?"., 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Item 1: Control of Advanced Manufacturing Technology: Supervision Without Supervisors?, 1987; Publication (Box 4, Folder 108)
      Author: Bernard Burnes and Mike Fitter
  - "QWL Innovation in Correctional Settings: A Review of Employee Concerns and an Initial Program Strategy"., 1980; Publication (Box 4, Folder 109)
    July 1980
    - Item 1: QWL Innovation in Correctional Settings: A Review of Employee Concerns and Initial Program Strategy, 1980; Publication (Box 4, Folder 109)
      Author: Thomas Burns
  - "The Federal Productivity Improvement Effort: Current Status and Future Agenda"., 1988; Publication (Box 4, Folder 110)
    Spring 1988
    - Item 1: The Federal Productivity Improvement Effort: Current Status and Future Agenda, 1988; Publication (Box 4, Folder 110)
      Author: Carolyn Burstein and Kathleen Sedlak
  - 1988, Publication (Box 4, Folder 111)
- Burstein, George - Childs, Laurence M., Ph D., Publication (Box 5)
  - "The Human Resource Manager--Productivity and the Quality of Work Life"., 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: The Human Resource Manager - Productivity and the Quality of Work Life, 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Author: George Burstein
  - Earning Inequality Over the Business Cycle., 1989; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    February 9 1989
    - Item 1: Earnings Inequality Over the Business Cycle, 1989; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Author: Gary Burtless
  - "Collective Bargaining for the Future"., 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    March - April 1987
    - Item 1: Collective Bargaining for the Future, 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Author: Cynthia Burton and Edward Cohen-Rosenthal
  - "Implementing QWL in Unionized Settings: The Basic Steps"., 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Impelmenting QWL in Unionized Settings: The Basic Steps, 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Author: Cynthia E. Burton and Edward Cohen-Rosenthal
      Notes: 3 copies in folder
  - "Labor-Management Relations and Productivity"., 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Relations and Productivity: A Framework for Success, 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Author: Daniel F. Burton and Sylvia Ann Hewlett
  - "The Group Process: Key to More Productive management"., 1981; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
    May 1981
    - Item 1: The Group Process: Key to More Productive Management, 1981; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Author: Gene E. Burton
  - "Relationships Between Group Temporality and Member Attitudes: Middle Managers and QWL Change Projects"., 1985; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Relationships Between Group Temporality and Member Attitudes: Middle Managers in QWL Change Projects, 1985; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Author: Gervase R. Bushe
  - "A Try at Steel-Mill Harmony"., 1981; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    June 29 1981
    - Item 1: A try at steel-mill harmony, 1981; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Organizing for Empowerment"., 1989; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Organizing for Empowerment, 1989; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Author: Gloria Busman
  - Organizing for Everything We Do., 1991; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Organizing for Everything We Do: CWA at AT&T and US West, 1991; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Author: Margaret Butler
  - "Cunning Moves in the Service Sector"., 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    June 1987
    - Item 1: Cunning moves in the service sector, 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Author: Matthew Butler
  - "Managing for Tomorrow"., 1985; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Summer 1985
    - Item 1: Managing for Tomorrow, 1985; Publication (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Author: Robert D. Buzzell and Mark J. Chussil
  - The Three Thrusts Toward Culture Change (Practical Suggestions for Turning Vision into Reality", 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Three Thrusts Toward Culture Change (Practical Suggestions for Turning Vision into Reality), 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Author: William C. Byham
  - "The Race to the Automatic Factory"., 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
    February 21 1983
    - Item 1: The Race to the Automatic Factory, 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Author: Gene Bylinsky
  - "Saving Time with New Technology"., 1991; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
    December 30 1991
    - Item 1: Saving Time with New Technology, 1991; Publication (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - "Turning off the Lights"., 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
    November 7 1983
    - Item 1: Turning off the lights: Managers bite the bullet and decide to close a moneylosing plant; So far, so good, but getting out poses lots of problems, 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Author: John A. Byrne
  - "How Japan Does It"., 1981; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
    March 30 1981
    - Item 1: How Japan Does It: The world's toughest competitor stirs a U.S. trade storm, 1981; Publication (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Author: Christopher Byron
  - The Automobile Manufacturing Enterprises Participating in the Present Case Study: Facts and Figures., 1984; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
    November 1984
    - Item 1: The Automobile Manufacturing Enterprises Participating in the Present Case Study: Facts and Figures, 1984; Publication (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - The Development and Utilization of Human resources in the Context of Technological Change and Industrial Restructuring., 1984; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
    October 11 1984
    - Item 1: The Development and Utilisation of Human Resources in the Context of Technological Change and Industrial Restructuring, 1984; Publication (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Sharpening Government's Response to Plant Closings., 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
    November 1979
    - Item 1: Sharpening Government's Response to Plant Closings: A Two Year Report on the Commerce-Labor Adjustment Action Committee, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Notes: 2 copies in folder
  - "Future Work"., 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Rewiring Your World: "Future Work", 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Notes: transcript
  - "Rewiring Your World"., 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 22)
    February - March 1983
    - Item 1: CWA Committee on Future Calls for Strategy-Driven Union, 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - The Alliance for Employee Growth and Development"., 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: The Alliance for Employee Growth and Development, Inc., 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - What is Quality of Work Life?, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: What Is Quality of Work Life?, Publication (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - "Winners and Losers in the Information Age"., 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Rewiring Your World II: "Winners and Losers in the Information Age", 1983; Publication (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - "CAlComp Reduces Product Development Cycle Time Using Teamwork"., 1991; Publication (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: CalComp Reduces Product Development Cycle Time Using Teamwork, 1991; Publication (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - "Remarks"., 1988; Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
    September 19 1988
    - Item 1: Remarks, 1988; Publication (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Author: Philip Caldwell
  - Planning Work: Resources on Technology and Investment., 1980; Publication (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Planning Work: Resources on technology and investment for labor education, 1980; Publication (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Women's Worth: Valuing Our Own Worth--Realizing Your Own Value., 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Women's Worth: Valuing Our Own Worth--Realizing Our Own Value, 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - "Refurbishing the Grievance Procedure Under Collective Bargaining"., 1984; Publication (Box 5, Folder 30)
    August 1984
    - Item 1: Refurbishing the Grievance Procedure Under Collective Bargaining, 1984; Publication (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Author: Robert J. Callaway
  - "Statement on Labor-Management Participation Teams in the Basic Steel Industry"., 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 31)
    April 23 1982
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Participation Teams in the Basic Steel Industry, 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Author: Sam Cames
  - "Steel--AN Industry at the Crossroads"., 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Steel--an industry at the crossroads, 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Author: Sam Camens
  - "Assessment of the Labor-Management Participation Teams Process in the Steel Industry"., 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
    March 12 1987
    - Item 1: Assessment of the Labor-Management Participation Teams Process in the Steel Industry, 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - "Reading the Customer Right"., 1991; Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
    December 2 1991
    - Item 1: Reading the Customer Right, 1991; Publication (Box 5, Folder 34)
      Author: Susan Caminiti
  - "Benchmarking: The Search for Industry Best Practices that Lead to Superior Performance"., 1990; Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: Benchmarking: The Search for Industry Best Practices That Lead to Superior Performance, 1990; Publication (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Author: Robert C. Camp
  - "Unlikely Partners: Company, Town and Gown"., 1985; Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
    November - December 1985
    - Item 1: Unlikely partners: Company, town, and gown, 1985; Publication (Box 5, Folder 36)
      Author: Lewis B. Campbell, J. Barry Mason, Joseph M. Mellichamp, and David M. Miller
  - "Can Workplace Democracy Boost Productivity?"., 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: Can Workplace Democracy Boost Productivity?, 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Micro technology and Employment: Issues of Concern to Women., 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
    July 1982
    - Item 1: Microtechnology and Employment: Issues of Concern to Women, 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Labor Adjustment in Canada: A Summary., 1986; Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Labour Adjustment in Canada: Summary, 1986; Publication (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - "Participative Management as a Foundation of Quality of Work Life -- Some Observations"., Publication (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Participative Management as a Foundation of Quality of Work Life -- Some Observations, Publication (Box 5, Folder 40)
      Author: Joseph P. Cangemi
  - "Japanese Challenge--American Response"., 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
    June 1 1987
    - Item 1: Japanese Challenge--American Response, 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 41)
      Author: Peter Cannon
  - "Bargaining in Telecommunications after Divestiture"., 1986; Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Bargaining in Telecommunications After Divestiture, 1986; Publication (Box 5, Folder 42)
      Author: Peter Cappelli and Charles Perry
  - Is Pattern Bargaining Dead?, 1990; Publication (Box 5, Folder 43)
    October 1990
    - Item 1: Is Pattern Bargaining Dead? A Discussion, 1990; Publication (Box 5, Folder 43)
      Author: Peter Cappelli
      Notes: response to 'Is Pattern Bargaining Dead?' by Kathryn J. Ready
  - "Satisfaction Market Wages, and the Restructuring of Labor Relations An Airline Study"., 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
    May 1987
    - Item 1: Satisfaction, Market Wages, and the Restructuring of Labor Relations: An Airline Study, 1987; Publication (Box 5, Folder 44)
      Author: Peter Cappelli and Peter D. Sherer
  - "A Practical Roadmap for High Performing Natural Work Teams"., 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
    June 1992
    - Item 1: Avoid Hitting the Potholes and Roadblocks to Team Excellence, Use A Practical Roadmap for High Performing Natural Teams, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 45)
      Author: Darlene Caplan, Darrell Givens, Greg Luff, Edward P. Kowel, James Sturrock, and Diane D. Worden
  - The Impact of Deregulation on the Employment and Wages of Airline Mechanics., 1986; Publication (Box 5, Folder 46)
    February 1986
    - Item 1: The Impact of Deregulation on the Employment and Wages of Airline Mechanics, 1986; Publication (Box 5, Folder 46)
      Author: David Card
  - "Union Versus Nonunion Attitudes Toward Share Arrangements"., Publication (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Union Versus Nonunion Attitudes Toward Share Arrangements, Publication (Box 5, Folder 47)
      Author: Laura B. Cardinal and I.B. Helburn
  - Industry Output and Job Growth Continues Slow into the Next Century., 1991; Publication (Box 5, Folder 48)
    November 1991
    - Item 1: Outlook: 1990-2005--Industry output and job growth continues slow into next century, 1991; Publication (Box 5, Folder 48)
      Author: Max L. Carey and James C. Franklin
  - "The Relationship Between Union Effectiveness and the Quality of Members' Worklife"., 1982; Publication (Box 5, Folder 49)